<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IoT on Project Flogo - Docs and Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IoT on Project Flogo - Docs and Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How-to for IOT</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/how-to/</guid>
      <description>Creating a flogo application is easy and we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined the steps for you in this howto guide. This guide will walk you through the steps required to create a simple flogo application which can also be used on an IOT device.
Prerequisites Before you can get started building IOT applications with flogo, you need to have the following prerequisites installed:
 The Go programming language should be installed. In order to simplify development and building in Go, we recommend using the gb build tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-pi/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a Raspberry Pi device. (https://www.raspberrypi.org/) This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for Raspberry Pi, you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARM=6 GOARCH=arm GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intel Edison</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-edison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-edison/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a Edison device. This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for Edison, you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARCH=386 GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:
SET GOARCH=386 SET GOOS=linux flogo build -o  This will compile your application and place the binary in the bin directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C.H.I.P</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-chip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-chip/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a C.H.I.P. device. (https://getchip.com/pages/chip) This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for C.H.I.P., you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARM=7 GOARCH=arm GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:
SET GOARM=7 SET GOARCH=arm SET GOOS=linux flogo build -o  This will compile your application and place the binary in the bin directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BeagleBone</title>
      <link>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-beaglebone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tibcosoftware.github.io/flogo/iot/device-beaglebone/</guid>
      <description>You can run your Flogo application on a BeagleBone device. (http://beagleboard.org/bone) This documents contains all relevant information on this device including how to build.
Build To build a flogo application for BeagleBone, you simply use the build command with the appropriate enviroment variables set.
On mac or linux you execute the following command:
env GOARM=7 GOARCH=arm GOOS=linux flogo build -o  On windows you excute the following commands:
SET GOARM=7 SET GOARCH=arm SET GOOS=linux flogo build -o  This will compile your application and place the binary in the bin directory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>